<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<component type="desktop-application">
<id>io.github.alamahant.Kerveros</id>
<name>Kerveros</name>
<summary>Secure 2FA Code Generator with Master Password Protection</summary>
<metadata_license>CC0-1.0</metadata_license>
<project_license>GPL-3.0-or-later</project_license>
<description>
<p>
Kerveros is a robust, cross-platform two-factor authentication (2FA) code generator that combines enterprise-grade security with user-friendly features. Generate time-based one-time passwords (TOTP) for all your online accounts while keeping your secrets encrypted and protected.
</p>
<p>
Key Features:
</p>
<ul>
<li>Master Password Protection: SHA-256 hashing with salting for enhanced security</li>
<li>Encrypted Secret Storage: XOR encryption with initialization vectors</li>
<li>TOTP Code Generation: RFC-compliant time-based one-time passwords</li>
<li>Real-time Code Updates: Automatic refresh every 30 seconds with visual countdown timer</li>
<li>QR Code Import: Drag and drop or file menu import of QR code images</li>
<li>One-Click Copy: Instant clipboard copy with visual feedback</li>
<li>Password Attempt Limiting: 5 attempts before factory reset option</li>
<li>System Tray Integration: Minimize to tray with quick restore</li>
<li>Export/Import Functionality: Full backup and restore capabilities</li>
<li>Single Instance Enforcement: Prevents multiple app conflicts</li>
</ul>
<p>
Kerveros is designed for security-conscious users who need a reliable, secure, and easy-to-use 2FA code generator with master password protection for all their online accounts including GitHub, Google, PayPal, Discord, and more.
</p>
</description>
<screenshots>
<screenshot type="default">
    <caption>Main view</caption>
    <image>https://raw.githubusercontent.com/alamahant/Kerveros/master/screenshots/Main_View.png</image>
  </screenshot>
</screenshots>
<launchable type="desktop-id">io.github.alamahant.Kerveros.desktop</launchable>
<url type="homepage">https://github.com/alamahant/Kerveros</url>
<url type="bugtracker">https://github.com/alamahant/Kerveros/issues</url>
<developer_name>Alamahant</developer_name>
<categories>
<category>Utility</category>
<category>Security</category>
<category>Office</category>
</categories>
<keywords>
<keyword>2FA</keyword>
<keyword>Security</keyword>
<keyword>OTP</keyword>
<keyword>TOTP</keyword>
<keyword>Authentication</keyword>
<keyword>Password</keyword>
<keyword>Encryption</keyword>
<keyword>QR Code</keyword>
<keyword>Qt</keyword>
<keyword>Cross-platform</keyword>
</keywords>
<content_rating type="oars-1.1">
<content_attribute id="social-info">mild</content_attribute>
</content_rating>
<releases>
<release version="1.0.0" date="2025-11-13">
<description>
<p>Initial release of Kerveros on Flathub.</p>
<ul>
<li>Master password protection with SHA-256 hashing and salting</li>
<li>Encrypted secret storage using XOR encryption</li>
<li>TOTP code generation with real-time updates</li>
<li>QR code import via drag and drop or file menu</li>
<li>One-click copy to clipboard with visual feedback</li>
<li>Password attempt limiting and factory reset protection</li>
<li>System tray integration and single instance enforcement</li>
<li>Export/import functionality for backup and restore</li>
<li>Cross-platform Qt interface</li>
</ul>
</description>
</release>
</releases>
<provides>
<binary>Kerveros</binary>
</provides>
<requires>
<display_length compare="ge">768</display_length>
</requires>
<recommends>
<control>keyboard</control>
<control>pointing</control>
</recommends>
</component>